[{"id": "5fd2d6d72596a59cbdfbd3ae", "question": "Which famous family member invented Lincoln Logs?", "answer": "Frank Lloyd Wright\"s son, John", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b9eb", "question": "Who is considered to be the creator of the \"Gran Turismo\" game series?", "answer": "Kazunori Yamauchi", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5af", "question": "What is the hardest substance in the human body?", "answer": "Enamel", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c90c", "question": "What is a calm ocean region near the equator called?", "answer": "Doldrums", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338aa9", "question": "Who wrote The Angel Doll: A Christmas Story in 1996?", "answer": "Jerry Bledsoe", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be81", "question": "Who was given a gift of a hat pin and a copy of \"Leaves of Grass\" on February 28, 1997?", "answer": "Monica Lewinsky", "category": "general"}, {"id": "601b4a1a49076251badbeaaf", "question": "Who was the first leader of the Republic of Texas?", "answer": "Sam Houston -- He later became one of Texas's first senators and then the state's governor.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb2b", "question": "What word refers to minimum attendance necessary for US Congress to conduct business?", "answer": "Quorum", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391a7", "question": "Who played Mad Max Rockatansky?", "answer": "Mel Gibson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59067b9aff9c0647b50a8066", "question": "What smartglasses were you able to purchase on November 10 2016, from a proprietary vending machine?", "answer": "Spectacles", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c324", "question": "What is glass mainly made up of?", "answer": "Sand", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bb7d", "question": "What trademarked name for in\u00adline skates was also its first successful brand name?", "answer": "Rollerblades", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe8ace301dd7bf43be5e771", "question": "What company created Mr. Pibb?", "answer": "Coca-Cola", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58ab192bbaab681b09292190", "question": "What is Donald Duck\u2019s car?", "answer": "A 1934 Belchfire Runabout", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4aa", "question": "Which country were the 1948 Summer Olympic Games held in?", "answer": "United Kingdom", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe4ed0d06d333868d34d769", "question": "What toy was originally created as a dog\u2019s chew toy?", "answer": "Rubber Duck", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fc991d875534e0fe3fe3c2b", "question": "Who said, \"I don't like to pay for the same real estate twice\"?", "answer": "General George S Patton", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f19", "question": "What author created Utopia?", "answer": "Thomas More", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fede0f56ce05a3942286dbf", "question": "In the film \"The Shawshank's Redemption,\" what was the name of the pet bird?", "answer": "Jake", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c1a3", "question": "What product was originally called \"Baby Gays\"?", "answer": "Q-Tips", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ff20f6631a458464a93c433", "question": "Who wrote the play \"A Streetcar Named Desire\"?", "answer": "Tennessee Williams", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bfe6", "question": "What country saw the origin of lawn tennis?", "answer": "England", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5febb4dd7e83c707845b211b", "question": "Why do snails produce slime?", "answer": "To stick to surfaces", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ed6", "question": "According to Langston Hughes, what might \"dry up, like a raisin in the sun\"?", "answer": "A dream deferred", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe4dcf306d333868d34d6fd", "question": "Who won four gold medals in the 1936 Olympics, infuriating Adolf Hitler?", "answer": "Jessie Owens", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b8be", "question": "What two animals are the symbols of the US Democrats and Republicans?", "answer": "Donkey and Elephant", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b767", "question": "What country traditionally goes last in the Olympic opening parade?", "answer": "The host country", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe733f0eec85e375820b229", "question": "What naval battle between Mark Antony and Octavian is often said to mark the beginning of the Roman Empire?", "answer": "Battle of Actium", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe1ecbc145fb29466707388", "question": "Where did fondue originate?", "answer": "Switzerland", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7c1", "question": "On what continent would you find the Great Victoria Desert?", "answer": "Australia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ff20f3c31a458464a93c42f", "question": "What novella was the inspiration for the film \"Apocalypse Now\"?", "answer": "\"Heart of Darkness\" by Joseph Conrad", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ab99c4821a8909e5c332d34", "question": "Who played Franz Liszt in the 1975 film \"Lisztomania\"?", "answer": "Roger Daltrey", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ff0", "question": "What film coined the term \"cameo appearance\" for a brief star turn in a movie?", "answer": "Around the World in Eighty Days", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ab1b3864fda37788a9a1dc3", "question": "Who wrote the novel \"Sparkling Cyanide\"?", "answer": "Agatha Christie", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398f5", "question": "What cartoon character was in love with his boss' daughter, Nell Fenwick?", "answer": "Dudley Do\u00adRight", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59cdb2dc65ff7d326b622a7a", "question": "Which Apollo space mission put the first men on the moon?", "answer": "Apollo 11", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c0a0", "question": "How many gallons does a tun barrel typically hold?", "answer": "252", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a689", "question": "Which US state is home to the manmade Fort Peck Lake?", "answer": "Montana", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be61", "question": "Avian flu in China led to 2006 price hikes in what piece of sporting equipment?", "answer": "Badminton birdies", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c613", "question": "Polaris is also referred to as what?", "answer": "The North Star", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f55", "question": "What James Joyce story collection begins with \"The Sisters\" and ends with \"The Dead\"?", "answer": "Dubliners", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a6c4", "question": "Lake Tahoe is located in which US states?", "answer": "California and Nevada", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338aaa", "question": "Who wrote the Christmas novel, The Lost Angel in 1971?", "answer": "Elizabeth Goudge", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113389a1", "question": "Which literary bear got its name from a London railway station?", "answer": "Paddington Bear", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5909cbbabb53d1af658864db", "question": "Which artist recorded the Christmas song \"Run Rudolph Run\" in 1958?", "answer": "Chuck Berry", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b913", "question": "Barbara Milicent Roberts is better known as?", "answer": "Barbie", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c53e", "question": "The bone patella is also known as what?", "answer": "The kneecap", "category": "science"}, {"id": "59774376284458f1d7854429", "question": "Who played Spock in the original Star Trek television series?", "answer": "Leonard Nimoy", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c363", "question": "What part of the body does an orthopedic doctor treat?", "answer": "Bones", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c110", "question": "What is the main ingredient of Tapenade?\u00a0", "answer": "Olives", "category": "general"}, {"id": "600b883a1d8c1817608d53ef", "question": "Which popular Mexican dish consists of chopped meat in a stew with red chillies and kidney beans?", "answer": "Chilli con carne", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a665", "question": "Pamlico Sound is located along the shores of which state?", "answer": "North Carolina", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b8aa", "question": "What country is the original home of Bacardi rum?", "answer": "Cuba", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe7ca3f877e98cb97778a04", "question": "What Cape will you find at the tip of Africa?", "answer": "Cape of Good Hope", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bbad", "question": "What two words did Jim Henson combine to come up with the word \"muppet\"?", "answer": "marionette and puppet", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398f6", "question": "What Beatles song begins with the opening fanfare from the French national anthem?", "answer": "All You Need is Love", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339190", "question": "What are Tom and Jerry?", "answer": "A Cat and a Mouse", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f5a", "question": "What New York cardiologist published his bestselling \"Diet Revolution\" in 1972?", "answer": "Robert Atkins", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59f9b844364247bf200fb87e", "question": "What year did Valve release the Steam platform?", "answer": "2003", "category": "general"}, {"id": "600cbffa6de0eb824d4052d6", "question": "Where is the world's largest greenhouse?", "answer": "Cornwall, England -- The Eden Project is home to more than one million plants. It features two hexagonally-patterned biomes.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392c4", "question": "In what film did a character named Pumpkin rob a restaurant while Vincent Vega was dining nearby?", "answer": "Pulp Fiction", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b3d5", "question": "Who was British Prime Minister at the outbreak of WWI?", "answer": "Herbert Henry Asquith", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac7a", "question": "What country's space travellers have been called \"taikonauts\" since 1998?", "answer": "China's", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c4cc", "question": "Which large animal can swim, but not jump?", "answer": "The elephant", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5cd40c7d685cf15b733e988f", "question": "What car manufacturer gave away their patent for the seat-belt in the interest of saving lives?", "answer": "Volvo", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe76c2beec85e375820b2cc", "question": "Which city is considered the perfume capital of the world?", "answer": "Grasse, France", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fea7e32ff048f679a45ac09", "question": "Automatonophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Human-like figures", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9f1", "question": "In which Mediterranean Sea are the Cyclades islands?", "answer": "The Aegean", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113394bb", "question": "Who played the role of Lamont Sanford in the TV show \"Sanford and Son\"?", "answer": "Desmond Wilson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133904f", "question": "Who composed \"Peter and the Wolf\"?", "answer": "Sergei Prokofiev", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fad", "question": "In ballet, a lowering of the body by bending the knee is called a what?", "answer": "Fondu", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "6015fb83fe83fe1f2a824c39", "question": "St. Patrick wrote in his Declaration that when he was 16 years what happened?", "answer": "According to his own writings, St. Patrick said he was was captured by Irish pirates when he was 16 years old.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe3e8c738e4e5d4832e630b", "question": "For what 1924 crime were Nathan Leopold, Jr. and Richard Loeb arrested?", "answer": "Murder", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397b1", "question": "What sitcom star did Mt. Airy, North Carolina rename a stretch of Highway 52 after, in 2002?", "answer": "Andy Griffith", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b296", "question": "Washington's famous crossing of the Delaware was en route to what Revolutionary War battle?", "answer": "The Battle of Trenton", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339573", "question": "What musical artist sang, It's the Most Wonderful Time of the Year?", "answer": "Andy Williams", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5febd5a27e83c707845b2163", "question": "What tool does Andy use in shaping his chess pieces in the movie \"The Shawshank Redemption\"?", "answer": "A rock blanket", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b9f", "question": "Who wrote the book \"Billy Budd\"?", "answer": "Herman Melville", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c043", "question": "What is podobromhidrosis?", "answer": "Smelly feet", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe4b53506d333868d34d6e7", "question": "What rocket launched the Apollo program?", "answer": "Saturn rocket", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a566", "question": "The Redwood National Park is located in which US state?", "answer": "California", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fd6656ca5bfecdd737e085f", "question": "What three vows do Catholic priests take?", "answer": "Poverty, chastity and obedience", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bb95", "question": "Since 1909, what women's magazine has guaranteed its advertiser\u2019s products with a \"seal of approval\"?", "answer": "Good Housekeeping", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b556", "question": "What is Hershey's most popular product?", "answer": "Reeses Peanut Butter Cup", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397f9", "question": "Which UK band had a 1974 hit with \"Billy Don't Be A Hero\"?", "answer": "Paper Lace", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113393ee", "question": "According to the 1973 movie, soylent green is what?", "answer": "People", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0fb", "question": "What major political scandal of the Harding administration involved a naval oil reserve on public land in Wyoming?", "answer": "The Teapot Dome Scandal", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1d7", "question": "Who traditionally occupied the Peacock Throne?", "answer": "The shah of Iran", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133929c", "question": "Apart from the piano, what other musical instrument does Dr. Sheldon Cooper from the TV show \"The Big Band Theory\"?", "answer": "The theramin", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a82d", "question": "What is the capital of Cambodia?", "answer": "Phnom Penh", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c528", "question": "How long does it take a human blood cell to make a complete circuit of the human body?", "answer": "One minute", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fa4", "question": "Poseidon was the Greek god of what?", "answer": "Sea", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fd96f4a23c87fd04dd15e41", "question": "Who were the first people known to celebrate the New Year?", "answer": "Babylonians", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f76", "question": "Which Shakespearean character has the most lines?", "answer": "Hamlet", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113395ad", "question": "In the 2003 remake of the movie \"The Italian Job\", the character played by which actor stole all the gold?", "answer": "Edward Norton", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c9a0", "question": "What is -459.67 F also know as?", "answer": "Absolute Zero", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d5c", "question": "What song did the Drifters follow with the 1964 sequel \"I've Got Sand in My Shoes\"?", "answer": "Under the Boardwalk", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b999", "question": "What is the capital of Nigeria?", "answer": "Abuja", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e38", "question": "In what film is General Jack Ripper obsessed with America's \"precious bodily fluids\"?", "answer": "Dr. Strangelove or: How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love the Bomb", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339050", "question": "Which Russian writer composed \"Peter and the Wolf\"?", "answer": "Sergei Prokofiev", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113394cb", "question": "Einstein was the name of what character's dog in the film \"Back to the Future\"?", "answer": "Emmett Brown", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f94", "question": "Who played the Keymaster in the movie \"Ghostbusters\"?", "answer": "Rick Moranis", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fef64996ce05a3942286e67", "question": "What is the smallest theater on Broadway?", "answer": "The Helen Hayes Theatre", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b9be", "question": "What is the name of the frog companion that you find in Donkey Kong Country?", "answer": "Winky", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5feccd5cec223966ae8f88ab", "question": "What bikini-clad seashell hunter does James Bond meet in \"Dr. No\"?", "answer": "Honey Ryder", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58ab15e4baab681b0929217f", "question": "What was the world\u2019s first mass-produced car to feature an all-aluminium body?", "answer": "Honda NSX", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a363", "question": "What is the capital of Bulgaria?", "answer": "Sofia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133933f", "question": "In what year did the TV show \"Grey's Anatomy\" premier?", "answer": "2005", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc17", "question": "What organization was formed to replace \"The League of Nations\"?", "answer": "United Nations", "category": "general"}, {"id": "600f754da9e54d890926f709", "question": "Minnesota, it is illegal to be what in bed?", "answer": "Naked", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c272", "question": "What is April's birthstone?", "answer": "Diamond", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c944", "question": "Who invented the kinetoscope?", "answer": "Louis Le Prince", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fd96dac23c87fd04dd15e2d", "question": "Who was the first person to fly around the world alone?", "answer": "Wiley Hardeman Post", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339337", "question": "How many children did Lucy and Desi have?", "answer": "Two", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c43", "question": "Who wrote \"The Cat in the Hat\" and \"Green Eggs and Ham\"?", "answer": "Dr. Seuss", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ffa3944c73aa70ea0b70ad9", "question": "Which city hosts the world's largest Passover Seder every year?", "answer": "Kathmandu", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac09", "question": "Which ocean does the Congo River empty into?", "answer": "Atlantic Ocean", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fed", "question": "What is the fear, or hatred of books called?", "answer": "Bibliophobia", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b7b0", "question": "What is the main flavoring ingredient in a typical gin recipe?", "answer": "Juniper berries", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ff50fc3d24dd593ee3eacc6", "question": "Which US state has the highest relative humidity?", "answer": "Alaska", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "58d47071f8e329de4f877891", "question": "What year was cricketer Phil Tufnell born?", "answer": "1966", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133967c", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", what movie star asked Homer to fix his movie?", "answer": "Mel Gibson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ad9db2ce748bb36357acdd7", "question": "On the Apollo 11 mission, what is the name of the man who never walked on the Moon?", "answer": "Michael Collins", "category": "science"}, {"id": "601b4b5749076251badbeac3", "question": "For what does NAACP stand?", "answer": "National Association for the Advancement of Colored People", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a722", "question": "What cave found in New Mexico, is the deepest cave in the continental US?", "answer": "Lechuguilla Cave", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339380", "question": "In the movie \"Interview with the Vampire\", what gift does Lestat give to Claudia every year?", "answer": "A doll", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c31b", "question": "Approximately how many kilometers are there in a nautical mile?", "answer": "1.85", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a71", "question": "What is the name of the milkman in \"Fiddler on the Roof\"?", "answer": "Tevye", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe8ef8601dd7bf43be5e7f3", "question": "What pasta gets its name because of its resemblance to a feather quill?", "answer": "Penne", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5f3058285aa2bc17b61b2ad5", "question": "In \"The Vampire Chronicles\" series of novels, what was Lestat's last name?", "answer": "de Lioncourt", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c221", "question": "What is the name of Canada's national anthem?", "answer": "O Canada", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ad7e7c7b24f84e0b9f9ffbe", "question": "By land area, which is Australia's largest territory?", "answer": "Australian Antarctic Territory", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339107", "question": "In the painting \"American Gothic\", who are the models said to have been modelled after?", "answer": "The painter's sister and his dentist", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fdc0e7d469bb8041d07a060", "question": "When a chef puts out every ingredient needed to prepare a dish ahead of time, what is it called?", "answer": "Mise En Place", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133cab1", "question": "What is the study of inland waters called?", "answer": "Limnology", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5e8", "question": "Mallard and Ruddy are species of what bird?", "answer": "Duck", "category": "science"}, {"id": "6000ed939a72b906b34e3cee", "question": "What is the name of the apparatus used to measure an unknown electrical resistance by balancing two legs of a circuit?", "answer": "The Wheatstone Bridge, named after its inventor, Sir Charles Wheatstone", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b772", "question": "How long is one furlong?", "answer": "1/8 mile / 220 yards", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113389b8", "question": "What musical instrument does Sherlock Holmes play for relaxation?", "answer": "Violin", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339806", "question": "By what name is the musician, Charles Hardin, better known as?", "answer": "Buddy Holly", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a268", "question": "Which actor played Mozart in the 1984 film \"Amadeus\"?", "answer": "Tom Hulce", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b0d", "question": "What does the comic book character Galactus eat?", "answer": "Planets", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59049db2cf93664eb10486b0", "question": "Who met in groups of 13, also called covens?", "answer": "Witches", "category": "general"}, {"id": "6010ca020775fa611bce67f1", "question": "Where was the first location of White Castle?", "answer": "Wichita, Kansas", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c3a2", "question": "What is an EKG?", "answer": "An electrocardiogram", "category": "science"}, {"id": "59ae9485574a5ce6b56b8249", "question": "\"Nobody Does it Better\" was the theme song of which Bond film?", "answer": "The Spy Who Loved Me", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5c90cf1f52800b05cac20f07", "question": "What US state receives the most annual rainfall?", "answer": "Hawaii", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b519", "question": "What religious day follows Halloween?", "answer": "All Saint's Day", "category": "general"}, {"id": "6010c9af0775fa611bce67ee", "question": "What\u2019s the main difference between a bay and bow window?", "answer": "Number of sections -- Bay windows usually have three sections while bow windows have anywhere from four to six.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba7e", "question": "What British holiday is celebrated on December 26th?", "answer": "Boxing Day", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58f16878f7c52aae91cc07c7", "question": "\"Cardice\" is another term for what?", "answer": "Dry ice", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a76e", "question": "The Gaza Strip extends northeast from what peninsula?", "answer": "Sinai Peninsula", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339048", "question": "Which Tennesee Williams play is about a Italian-American woman?", "answer": "The Rose Tattoo", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe76894eec85e375820b2a2", "question": "Which two U.S. national parks are located within the Arctic Circle?", "answer": "Gates of the Arctic National Park and Kobuk Valley National Park", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fea3db3ff048f679a45ab50", "question": "Something that is toward the end or away from the center of the body can also be called what?", "answer": "Distal", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a57", "question": "The 2006 Mel Gibson movie \"Apocalypto\" concerns the demise of what ancient empire?", "answer": "The Mayan Empire", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5b7ffb9a3a3a814d89068c67", "question": "Which singer and songwritter was born Farrokh Bulsara in 1946?", "answer": "Freddie Mercury", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab87", "question": "What country is Phnom Penh the capital of?", "answer": "Cambodia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59f9b7d1364247bf200fb877", "question": "Which Canadian city was originally called Bytown?", "answer": "Ottawa", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b7d0", "question": "What is a turkey stuffed with a duck stuffed with a chicken called?", "answer": "Turducken", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd6a7796c0f9723ab15cb5f", "question": "How many US dollars are a pound of dimes and a pound of quarters each worth?", "answer": "$20 each", "category": "general"}, {"id": "597743cf284458f1d785442b", "question": "What city is the capital of Mississippi?", "answer": "Jackson", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c35b", "question": "How many feet do snails have?", "answer": "One", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aab3", "question": "Which bird is the national bird of Denmark?", "answer": "Mute swan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "590682e5ff9c0647b50a80a1", "question": "What popular mobile game, that caused many players to get into accidents, was released in July of 2016?", "answer": "Pokemon Go", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdca", "question": "What off-road endurance race is named after the African capital where it usually ends?", "answer": "The Dakar Rally", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9df", "question": "What is a calm ocean region near the equator called?", "answer": "Doldrums", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388ec", "question": "What is the technical name of the pound sign?", "answer": "Octothorpe", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b3fa", "question": "What year did James Garfield start and end his presidency?", "answer": "1881", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe7c7f0877e98cb977789d9", "question": "Which country is known as the \"Hashemite Kingdom\"?", "answer": "Jordan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fea34ceff048f679a45aafc", "question": "Which is the oldest planet in our solar system?", "answer": "Jupiter", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c624", "question": "What shape is the milky way?", "answer": "Spiral", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b179", "question": "In what year was the Sydney Opera House designated as a UNESCO World Heritage Site?", "answer": "2007", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a78", "question": "What William Faulkner novel presented its plot from four different points of view?", "answer": "The Sound and the Fury", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113399bb", "question": "What was the name of the Clampett\u2019s dog on \"The Beverly Hillbillies\"?", "answer": "Duke", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fde52b6c6c6b019850c9a98", "question": "In Proverbs, when Solomon refers to the lazy, he tells the sluggard to look to what insect for an example?", "answer": "Ant", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133944c", "question": "Mel Gibson both directed and starred in which 1995 movie?", "answer": "Braveheart", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58d117f44fea7fe947a2227f", "question": "The pivot point of a lever is called what?", "answer": "Fulcrum", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab8f", "question": "What countries share land borders with Cambodia?", "answer": "Thailand, Laos and Vietnam", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ff0b299e662d71a53650fda", "question": "What is James Bond's preferred type of martini?", "answer": "Vesper", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ffb668f5dad637d903c8838", "question": "The Maluku islands (informally known as the Spice Islands) belong to which country?", "answer": "Indonesia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133cae8", "question": "What is the study of soils in their natural environment called?", "answer": "Pedology", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5b6992cbe762b54eb9be9426", "question": "What country has the calling code +20?", "answer": "Egypt", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ae3", "question": "Which French artist, born in 1834 was best known for his paintings of ballet dancers?", "answer": "Edgar Degas", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "590721e13745b36be73039fb", "question": "Which Disney character is named after Ebenezer from Charles Dickens\u2019 novel \"A Christmas Carol\"?", "answer": "Scrooge McDuck", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab1b", "question": "What is the official language of Cuba?", "answer": "Spanish", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5afad7f8430e050a5df0d111", "question": "What is emitted from a nuclear reaction that can cause another fission?", "answer": "A Neutron", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5a25ef876682715b82711cd7", "question": "\"Photo Journal\" was a weekly newspaper written and sold in which country until 1981?", "answer": "Canada", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339888", "question": "What colour was Oscar the Grouch during the first season of Sesame Street?", "answer": "Orange", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a23b", "question": "Who released the 1970's album entitled \"Madman Across the Water\"?", "answer": "Elton John", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b102", "question": "What was explorer Ponce de Leon's first name?", "answer": "Juan", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ae28", "question": "In which decade was the Panama Canal completed?", "answer": "1910s", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5febd9ee7e83c707845b217f", "question": "In the film \"The Shawshank Redemption,\" what did Andy write in the Bible for warden Norton to read after he had escaped?", "answer": "Dear Warden, you were right. Salvation lay within.", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59decf99ea2747c8aff16d20", "question": "Myomancy is the practice of what?", "answer": "Reading omens from the behavior of rats or mice", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bff0", "question": "Where were fortune cookies invented?", "answer": "United States", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab61", "question": "What city is associated with Alcatraz?", "answer": "San Francisco", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339978", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", where was Lenny born?", "answer": "Chicago", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca1b", "question": "Filbert is an alternative name for which nut?", "answer": "Hazelnut", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5a4a98fa61d1b4d384d5d694", "question": "What year did the radio show \"Gunsmoke\" debut as a TV show?", "answer": "1955", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a72f", "question": "The Simi Valley is located in which US state?", "answer": "California", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a31", "question": "Who played the title role in the 1962 award-winning film \"Lawrence of Arabia\"?", "answer": "Peter O\u2019Toole", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5be57fc05415ba52ed6f0aae", "question": "What crop is attacked by the Colorado beetle?", "answer": "Potato", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a1d4", "question": "What is Billie Holiday's birth name?", "answer": "Eleanora Fagan", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6d7", "question": "What professor of physics oversaw the design and assembly of the first atomic bomb?", "answer": "J. Robert Oppenheimer", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe69f1720565ad31a57c78a", "question": "The first woman to run for president chose whom as her running mate?", "answer": "Fredrick Douglas", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe1f020145fb2946670738f", "question": "Popcorn comes in which two general shapes?", "answer": "Mushroom and butterfly", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391c2", "question": "What is Marilyn Monroe's real name?", "answer": "Norma Jeane Mortenson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c976", "question": "What does an ombrometer measure?", "answer": "Rainfall", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aeaa", "question": "Which German Nazi was known as the butcher of Lyon?", "answer": "Klaus Barbie", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5909cf7abb53d1af658864f4", "question": "In the film \"Home Alone 2\", what city was the McCallister family planning on vacationing in?", "answer": "Miami", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ce2", "question": "At what US city did Bugs Bunny traditionally lament taking a left \"toin\"?", "answer": "Albuquerque", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac71", "question": "Where were scissors believed to be first invented?", "answer": "Ancient Egypt", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113395db", "question": "In The Simpsons, what is the name of the baseball bat Homer makes himself?", "answer": "Wonderbat", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c995", "question": "What is \"bovine spongiform encephalopathy\" more commonly known as?", "answer": "Mad cow disease", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396b0", "question": "What Oscar-winning Best Picture is named for a type of rose?", "answer": "American Beauty", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5989a862cb8751d53e7d75f9", "question": "United States' observation of Mardi Gras was started in which city and state?", "answer": "Mobile, Alabama", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338aac", "question": "Who wrote the Christmas mystery, The Bishop and the Three Kings?", "answer": "Andrew Greeley", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339088", "question": "What colour was Moby Dick?", "answer": "White", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ddf", "question": "What kind of wine accompanies Hannibal Lecter's liver and fava bean dinner?", "answer": "Chianti", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339108", "question": "Who wrote the book \"Man's Search for Meaning\"?", "answer": "Viktor E. Frankl", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fede6516ce05a3942286dfc", "question": "What Tim Burton movie follows a mischievous ghost famed for his striped suit?", "answer": "\"Beetlejuice\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339091", "question": "In Greek mythology, what was Hades the god of?", "answer": "Underworld", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a416", "question": "What West Coast city was home to Jack Murphy Stadium?", "answer": "San Diego", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6007815fbd51d85e222ab64b", "question": "What art movement employs aspects of mass culture, such as advertising, comic books and mundane cultural objects?", "answer": "Seeking to elevate popular culture to the level of fine art,\u00a0Pop artists\u00a0celebrated commonplace objects and everyday people.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab5a", "question": "What sea does the river Elbe flow into?", "answer": "North Sea", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe76664eec85e375820b27f", "question": "Which country is Great Barrier Island part of?", "answer": "New Zealand", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bad1", "question": "How many years does a sesquicentennial celebrate?", "answer": "150", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339225", "question": "Who plays the role of Craig the puppeteer's wife in \"Being John Malkovich\"?", "answer": "Cameron Diaz", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a980", "question": "What Danish peninsula lent its name to the largest naval battle of World War I?", "answer": "Jutland", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ff1", "question": "Fred Astaire's character in \"Funny Face\" was based on what fashion photographer?", "answer": "Richard Avedon", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a5a", "question": "What is the name of the character that can be used in place of the word \"and\"?", "answer": "Ampersand", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b065", "question": "One\u00ad-third of all the US Marines that died during World War II died on what island?", "answer": "Iwo Jima", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a32e", "question": "Who released the album \"Tigermilk\"?", "answer": "Belle and Sebastian", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb5d", "question": "What ice cream chain once sold a ketchup-flavored ice cream?", "answer": "Baskin-Robbins", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca61", "question": "What name is given to the diagram in which sets are represented by circles?", "answer": "Venn Diagram\u00a0", "category": "science"}, {"id": "59e3f7405cb9e8bda682136e", "question": "What year was the wreck of the Titanic discovered?", "answer": "1985", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9c8", "question": "Which US state has the least rainfall?", "answer": "Nevada", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "58ab18e2baab681b0929218f", "question": "Which car manufacturer produces the Clio?", "answer": "Renault", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113394db", "question": "Who played the role of Kevin Arnold on \"The Wonder Years\"?", "answer": "Fred Savage", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a1c2", "question": "Which artist married Carrie Fisher in 1983?", "answer": "Paul Simon", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf0e", "question": "In what sport would you perform an Adolf?", "answer": "Trampolining forward 3.5 twists", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf02", "question": "What animal is the mascot of the US Naval Academy?", "answer": "The goat", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b96", "question": "What actor built a working full\u00adsize painter's studio for himself in preparation for his role as a famous artist?", "answer": "Ed Harris", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c669", "question": "Who developed the light bulb while working in his Menlo Park laboratory?", "answer": "Thomas Edison", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339213", "question": "What is the make of the car used as a time machine in the movie \"Back to the Future\"?", "answer": "DeLorean", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b714", "question": "In the song Santa Claus is Coming to Town, what does Santa know?", "answer": "When you're awake and if you've been bad or good", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113393e5", "question": "Guitarist Brian May was part of what popular band?", "answer": "Queen", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d2d", "question": "The novel \"A Brave New World\" is set in what year?", "answer": "2540", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133924b", "question": "Who performed the Bond theme song \"Die Another Day\"?", "answer": "Madonna", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c226", "question": "What ingredients are needed to make a standard Mai Tai cocktail?", "answer": "Light rum, dark rum, lime juice, orgeat syrup and orange curacao", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb3f", "question": "How many squares are on a checker board?", "answer": "64", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b9a7", "question": "What baseball player was nicknamed \"Joltin' Joe\" and the \"Yankee Clipper\"?", "answer": "Joe DiMaggio", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e1e", "question": "The last two surviving jurors from the film \"12 Angry Men\" were actors who shared what first name?", "answer": "Jack", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113390b3", "question": "Which book has the statement \"all pigs are equal, but some pigs are more equal than others\"?", "answer": "Animal Farm", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339654", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", what is the name of Fat Tony's establishment?", "answer": "The Legitimate Businessmen's Social Club", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a62f", "question": "What is the two letter postal abbreviation for Massachusetts?", "answer": "MA", "category": "geography"}]